(Sheldon:)Do they know it's there?
Um, sh-should I tell somebody?
(Amy:)It's there on purpose.
(Amy:)It's refreshing.
(Sheldon:)Interesting.
(Sheldon:)The world's most boring liquid
(Sheldon:)and the world's
most boring vegetable.
(Sheldon:)But you put 'em together,
and bleh.
(Leonard:)Hey.
Hi.
Oh! Good, you're here.
Are you still fighting?
(Sheldon:)If you get divorced,
do I get two Christmases?
(Penny:)We're not getting divorced.
(Leonard:)Listen, we realized, that, uh...
(Leonard:)we're facing some new challenges
(Leonard:)as a married couple.
(Penny:)Yeah. And there are a few things
(Penny:)we need to stay on top of.
So we thought
(Penny:)it would useful...
(Penny:)and I can't believe
I am about to say this...
(Amy:)um...
(Leonard:)Would you please help us
make a Relationship Agreement?
(Leonard:)But one that's tailored to us.
Okay? We don't need
a bathroom schedule.
(Penny:)Although a rule about him
texting me from in there
(Penny:)might help with the romance.